musicroom.fr 2006-12-11

# Musicroom.com - Sheet Music for Musicians

Musicroom.com is committed to keeping the personal details of its visitors and customers private and secure (information is collected and stored in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). 

**We will not sell or share your personal details with unrelated third parties, partners or affiliates, without explicitly asking for your consent in advance.**

The type of information we will collect about you includes: 

  * your name 
  * address 
  * phone number 
  * email address 

We use the personal information you give us for the following purposes: 

  * to contact you about the status of your order. 
  * to efficiently process and dispatch your order to your delivery address. 
  * to change and enhance the web site. 
  * to occasionally email you with details of our products, special promotions, and enhancements. If you would prefer not to receive these mailings, then please send an email to [info@musicroom.com](mailto:info@musicroom.com) with the subject line 'Unsubscribe'. Please note that we will only send email to people who have opted in to receive it and where we are replying to an email query.
  * to conduct anonymous and aggregate research into a) the way our web site is used and b) the purchasing patterns of our customers. 

We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings. Note that if you modify your browser to refuse cookies from Musicroom.com, parts of the web site may not function as expected. For more information about cookies and how to control them, please visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. 

If you have any questions about Musicroom.com's privacy policy please email them to [info@musicroom.com](mailto:info@musicroom.com)

**Platform of Privacy Preferences**

As well as the above Privacy Policy we offer a **P3P** Privacy Policy that can be automatically be read and interpreted by the latest browser software. P3P is an industry standard developed by the [World Wide Web Consortium](http://www.w3.org/P3P/) providing a simple, automated way for users to gain more control over the use of personal information on Web sites they visit. P3P enabled browsers can "read" this snapshot automatically and compare it to your own set of privacy preferences. 

Our machine-readable P3P Policy is located here: www.musicroom.com/W3C/privacy_policy.xml. 

We have also translated the P3P Policy into English: www.musicroom.com/W3C/privacy_policy.aspx.
